doperoms.co.uk 2009-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Doperoms.com

207 Online

**Language:** 

The Rom Archive

Advertisement

**DopeROMs.com Privacy Statement**  
  
---  
  
During the process of delivering our service to you, DopeROMs.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number. However, DopeROMs.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by DopeROMs.com is used for the purpose of demographics. 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, DopeROMs.com may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, DopeROMs.com may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.

Doperoms.com may employ the use of cookies to track membership information. All information collected by doperoms.com is used only by doperoms.com. Your information is **Never Sold** or _Distributed_ to any third party. We will honor this agreement by destroying your information before giving it away. That means anyone not working directly with doperoms.com will never see any of your information.

Doperoms.com does not guarantee any files linked on doperoms.com are clean and virus free. It is your responsibility to scan files you download. Please report any infected links to the administrator. By downloading a file link on doperoms.com you agree that doperoms.com or parties associated with doperoms.com may not be held responsible for loss or corruption of information or hardware when using this site. USE AT YOUR OWN RISK!

Privacy Policy \- [Contact](http://doperoms.com/contact.php) \- Frequently Asked Questions

DMCA Policy \- Advertise on DopeRoms \- Site Map

Copyright DopeROMS.com 2009 All Rights Reserved | Content Copyright Respective Owners   
Compression: No | Cache: On | Database: On | 9 Queries Used | 9.1 Seconds.
